<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Liz Kariuki</title>
    <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Liz Kariuki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 14:59:37 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lizkariuki.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is Mainstream Medicine Evil</title>
      <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/is-mainstream-medicine-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 14:59:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/is-mainstream-medicine-evil/</guid>
      <description>Is Mainstream Medicine Evil? How Drugs Come to Market This summarises the 10th chapter of Bad Science by Ben Goldacre: Is Mainstream Medicine Evil? The chapter explains the tricks used by pharmaceutical companies while they conduct expensive drug trials to make their products seem better than they are. Big pharma is one of the most distrusted sectors of the economy and modern healthcare. It is therefore important to understand how ‘evil’ they are to know how best to counter it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Fish and Winden</title>
      <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/of-fish-and-winden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 12:28:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/of-fish-and-winden/</guid>
      <description>Of Fish and Winden So, you know how fish don&amp;rsquo;t exist?
No?
Okay, let me start over.
 The Nobel Prize winning biologist Stephen Jay Gould concluded after a lifetime&amp;rsquo;s studying of fish that there is no such thing as a fish. He reasoned that while there are many things that live in the sea, most of them are not related to each other. For example, a salmon is more closely related to a camel than to a hagfish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anchor Earn</title>
      <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/anchor-earn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:58:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/anchor-earn/</guid>
      <description>How To Deposit Funds into Anchor Earn Anchor Earn on the Terra network is one of the safest way to park money in crypto and earn a guaranteed return. It is &amp;lsquo;a decentralized savings protocol offering low-volatile yields on Terra stablecoin deposits&amp;rsquo;. At time of writing, there is $14 billion locked in Anchor earning an interest of 19.46% APY. In this guide I will show you how to go from Kenya shillings to UST in Anchor&amp;rsquo;s Earn protocol; a process that requires a few steps that can be daunting for a beginner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Need a Budget</title>
      <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/ynab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:29:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/ynab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Book Notes for You Need a Budget by Jesse Mecham.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Host a Hugo Site for Free on Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/hugo-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 11:33:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lizkariuki.com/posts/hugo-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Find out how to create a Hugo site and host it on Github Pages for free.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
